[{"question": "  i\u0092m ready!", "answer": " you sure?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " uh-huh!", "answer": " okay, let me just straighten out your helmet there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": "  thanks daddy.", "answer": " no-no, one daddy, two mommies. all right, it\u0092s all yours.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " okay. okay.", "answer": " yes! yes! yes!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " his first big kid\u0092s bike, this is so exciting!", "answer": " oh yeah, i remember mine! ohh, it was my sixth birthday, my dad took me to the park, i got it, and\u009ait bent.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " i never had a bike of my own.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": "  what?!", "answer": " well, we didn\u0092t have a lot of money. but the girl across the street had the best bike! it was pink and it had rainbow colored tassels hanging off the handle grips, and-and-and a bell and this big, white wicker basket with those plastic daisies stuck on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " that sounds like my first bike.  my dad gave me his old one.", "answer": " ohh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " did the girl ever let you ride it?", "answer": " no! but she gave me the box that it came in. it had a picture of the bike on the front.  so i would sit on it and my step-dad would drag me around the backyard.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " that is so unfair!", "answer": " not really, i got to drag him around too!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " hey! what are you guys doing?", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " making holiday candy for the neighbors.", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry, who?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " i\u0092m gonna hang this basket  on the door and when the neighbors walk by they can all take a piece.", "answer": " but we don\u0092t know the neighbors.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " i do. there\u0092s uh, let\u0092s see, guy with a mustache, smokes-a-lot lady, some kids i\u0092ve seen, and a red-haired guy who does not like to be called rusty.", "answer": " see? this is exactly why i\u0092m making this candy. we can learn their names and get to know our neighbors.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " wouldn\u0092t it be easier if we just moved?", "answer": "  gooood morning!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " eh, somebody\u0092s in a good mood!", "answer": " well, why shouldn\u0092t i be? i have great friends! i have a wonderful job!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " where you can make out with your assistant.", "answer": " come on, it\u0092s not a big deal! we stayed up all night coming up with a plan so that us dating will not be a problem.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " oh yeah, what\u0092s the plan?", "answer": "  we\u009a we are not\u009a \u009agoing to let it\u009a be a problem.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " wow! it took you all night to come up with that plan?!", "answer": " well y\u0092know, we did other stuff too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " did you two\u009a", "answer": " oh monica come on, y\u0092know i don\u0092t sleep with guys on the first date!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " matt guire, mark lynn, ben wire\u009a", "answer": " anymore!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " hi. tag, i have a conference call today is that correct?", "answer": " yes, at 4:00.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " i\u0092d better get back to my desk.", "answer": " okay, you hard worker! i\u0092ll remember to put that in your evaluation.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " my what?", "answer": " well, you\u0092ve been here for two months now and your boss is required to hand in a performance evaluation. but y\u0092know, there is one thing that i have yet to evaluate.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " are you serious?", "answer": " no, i\u0092ve just always wanted to do that. can you help me clean this up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " the basket is totally empty! my god, the neighbors ate all the candy!", "answer": " well, either that or uh\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " did you eat all the neighbor candy?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " uh well yeah, that was the plan, but by the time i got to it there was only a couple of pieces left!", "answer": " yeah, and they\u0092ve been coming by all day. they love it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " ross! the neighbors ate all my candy!!", "answer": " mine stole my newspaper! it\u0092s like a crime wave!!  pheebs, you uh, you got a second.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " sure!", "answer": " yeah, ever since you uh, told me that story about that bike i-i couldn\u0092t stop thinking about it. i mean, everyone should have a-a first bike, so\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": "  oh my god ross!!", "answer": " you like it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " i love it!!", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " ohh!! ohh!! and i love you!", "answer": " ahh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " not that way! but the bike brought you a lot closer!", "answer": " ah!  well uh-uh, t-take it downstairs, y\u0092know give it a test ride.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " okay! oh my god! my first bike! thank you for the best present i\u0092ve ever gotten.", "answer": "  you\u0092re welcome.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": "  oh and chandler\u0092s about to cry.", "answer": "  am not!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": "  who is that?!", "answer": " don\u0092t worry, i\u0092m brave! i am brave! i\u009ai am brave!  no-no-no-no!!   can you tell me who is there please?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hi. do you know what time it is?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " it\u0092s candy time! my roommate says that they taste like little drops of heaven.", "answer": " oh please!  did you hear that? little drops of heaven.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": "  4:00 a.m.", "answer": " so, can i get some candy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " i am sorry, but some of us have to get up early and go to work!   he does not know that i am not some of us.", "answer": " umm, listen i am sorry, but i\u0092ll put some out first thing in the morning.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " well okay, i\u0092ll swing by later. do you live in this building?", "answer": " um-hmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": "  mm! seems like i would\u0092ve remembered you!", "answer": " mm! night gar\u0092!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": "  so did you read your evaluation yet?", "answer": " no! it was marked confidential i just sent it down to human resources.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": "  okay please, you\u0092re kidding right?! i wrote that one as a joke for you!", "answer": " a joke they would appreciate?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " i\u0092m thinkin\u0092 no.", "answer": " what did you say?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " umm, i said i thought you were a good kisser, and uh, and that i like your tiney-tiny touchie.", "answer": " no, not my touchie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " ross! that is so sweet of you to get phoebe that bike! when i heard the story, i almost cried.", "answer": " almost cried huh? hear that chandler? almost cried!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " hey, you cry every time somebody talks about titanic!", "answer": "  those two only had each other!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " phoebe really likes the bike huh?", "answer": " oh yeah! i saw her walkin\u0092 it down the street the other day. she had uh, these flowers in the basket. it was so cute.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " yeah, i saw her this morning walkin\u0092 it by the park.", "answer": " wait a minute, she was walking the bike? both times?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " hey pheebs?", "answer": " oh hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " hey! so are you enjoying the bike?", "answer": " ohh, uh-huh so much!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " pheebs you uh\u009ayou do know how to ride a bike don\u0092t you?", "answer": " of course!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " umm, can we see you ride it?", "answer": " okay.  see? commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " see, this is why i told you never get involved with your assistant! and here is no such thing as keeping secrets when it comes to affairs.  did you hear that chandler? no such thing!", "answer": "  what happened? i\u0092m just eating candy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " maybe it\u0092s not as bad as i think. y\u0092know, maybe they didn\u0092t take it the way i meant it.", "answer": " absolutely! y\u0092know, because touchie can mean both ass and good worker.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " ugh, i just gotta get the thing back!", "answer": " hey rach?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " that sketch you mentioned? might it have looked a little something like this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " oh my god! joey!", "answer": " what is the matter with you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " ugh!", "answer": " boy i tell ya, this little talent came in handy before i could afford porn.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " hi! i\u0092m sorry, i know it\u0092s after hours but i really need candy.", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry, i can\u0092t help you. see?  rules are rules.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " please! i have people coming from out of town today! and, i told them all about your candy!", "answer": " no kidding, out of towners huh? what did you tell \u0091em?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " i told \u0091em your candy is absolutely indescribable!", "answer": " some people have been saying its y\u0092know little drops of heaven, but whatever.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " please, can\u0092t you help me out?", "answer": "  hey chandler, do we know that lady?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " maybe, isn\u0092t she the woman who lives below you and has sex really loud?", "answer": "  all right, i\u0092ll do it just this once! but you can\u0092t tell anybody!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": "  yes! yes! please, just give it to joey and chandler: yeah, that\u0092s her.", "answer": "  thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": "  it\u0092s unbelievable! i-i can\u0092t believe that sign didn\u0092t work!", "answer": " y\u0092know what would work?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " hmm?", "answer": " stop making candy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " but they like it!", "answer": " you mean they like you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " maybe.", "answer": " is that why you became a chef? so that people would like you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " okay, now just remember everything i taught you and you\u0092ll be fine. okay? here we go. ready\u009aset\u009a", "answer": "  wait! this seat is really uncomfortable! yeah, maybe before we start we should just get another one. perhaps, like an airplane seat\u0097or a beanbag chair!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " phoebe, you can\u0092t get out of this! okay? you have to learn how to ride a bike!", "answer": " why? why do i have to learn?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " well\u009ain-in case of emergency.", "answer": " what kind of an emergency?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " well let there\u0097what if a man comes along and puts a gun to your head and says, \"you ride this bike or i\u0092ll sh\u009ai\u0092ll shoot you.\"", "answer": " okay, i would ring the bell to distract him and then i would knock the gun out of his hand with a chinese throwing star.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " okay, phoebe just-just get-get on the bike and\u0097hey! i\u0092ll hold you up and-and push you. okay?", "answer": " you won\u0092t let go?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " no!", "answer": " swear?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " i swear!", "answer": "  okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " all right.", "answer": " all right. feel good?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " well\u009a", "answer": " all right, try pedaling.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " that\u0092s it, your doing great.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " doing great! yes-yes-yes! take control! yes!", "answer": " weee!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " oh! oh! oh no!! you swore!", "answer": " i-i just thought you were doing so well. i\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " hey, there\u0092s uh, some people outside, askin\u0092 about candy.", "answer": " well, they\u0092re just gonna have to wait aren\u0092t they? i\u0092ve only got two hands!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " need some help?", "answer": " no! you don\u0092t know the system! there\u0092ll be nobody messing with the system!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": "  oh, hello liar.", "answer": "  look, i-i\u0092m really sorry i let go of the bike.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " i could\u0092ve been killed i hope you know!", "answer": " i know. i know. but, can we please try it again? huh? i mean, you were so close phoebe!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " phoebe.", "answer": " what?!  what the hell?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " all right, y\u0092know what? if you are not going to learn how to ride this bike then i\u0092m sorry, i\u0092m just gonna have to take it back.", "answer": " what?! why?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " because! because, it-it-it\u0092s\u009a it\u0092d be like you having this guitar  and-and never playing it. okay, this guitar wants to be played! and-and this bike wants to be ridden and-and if you don\u0092t ride it you-you\u0092re-you\u0092re killing its spirit!  the bike is dying.", "answer": " all right. if you care enough to make up that load of crap, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " great! great!  you\u0092re making the bike very happy.", "answer": "  okay ross!  please don\u0092t die!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " okay, i think we can get the evaluation back before they see it, but we\u0092re gonna have to get into mr. zelner\u0092s office. now, he doesn\u0092t get in until 10, so he\u0092s no problem, but his assistant, betty, she comes in early to eat her breakfast at her desk.", "answer": " that\u0092s kinda sad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " yeah, well betty\u0092s kinda sad. which is why i believe i can lure her away with these chocolates.  now, while i distract her, you get in the office.", "answer": " got it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " hello rachel, you uh, got a minute?", "answer": "  yeah, sure mr. zelner, for you anything\u0097minute. okay. fine.  abort the plan, abort the plan.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " uh actually, i\u0092d like to speak with both of you.", "answer": " okay. uh, well can we, can we get you anything mr. zelner? maybe some chocolates?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " umm, no. thanks, but i\u0092ll give these to betty.  so i read your evaluation of tag, or to use his full name, tag sweetcheeks jones. is something going on with you two?", "answer": "  oh my god. can you imagine if there was?! i mean,  what would happen exactly.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " well, i\u0092d be forced to file a report. i\u0092d have to consult with the legal department, and your future at the company would be in jeopardy.", "answer": " well\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": "  uh mr. zelner, i\u0092m the one who filled in that evaluation.", "answer": " oh no-no-no\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": "  yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah, i thought it would be funny.", "answer": " you wrote that you have a cute touchie?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": "  yes. i have a weird sense of humor, and i\u0092m kinda strangely proud of my butt.", "answer": " it\u0092s kind of a risky joke tag, and what is-what is this drawing i can\u0092t figure out what this is?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " you\u0092re lookin\u0092 at it upside down\u0097y\u0092know what?  it doesn\u0092t matter.", "answer": " yeah, it\u0092s not like i don\u0092t have a sense of humor, huh? hell, i even enjoy a naughty limerick now and then. but there\u0092s a time and a place, huh?! unless you uh, have a limerick right now?  no? okay, well uh, you\u0092ve  got my fax number.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " whoa! i can\u0092t believe you did that. that was really sweet.", "answer": " no, don\u0092t worry about it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " no, you could\u0092ve lost your job.", "answer": " are you kidding me?! with a cute butt like this, i\u0092d find work.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " y\u0092know what?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " i feel great.  in fact!  what?", "answer": " i\u009a it just\u0097it took me so long to get that desk organized.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": "  what is going on?", "answer": " we\u0092re waiting for the candy.  bring out the candy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " yeah lady! give us candy!!", "answer": " joey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " what\u0092s up buddy?", "answer": " what are you doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " waiting for candy.", "answer": " get in here!  hey, and you can not smoke in here!   merry christmas.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": "  okay, guys! the candy is coming; i just need another 15 minutes for the chocolate to cool!", "answer": " we want candy! we want candy now!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " all right everybody! just be quiet! be quiet! be quiet!! pipe-pipe-pipe down!  what is the matter with you people?! this woman was trying to do a nice thing for you. she was making candy so she could try to get to know all of you, and i\u0092ll bet that not one of you can tell me her name! am i right?", "answer": "  candy lady?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " no not  candy lady.", "answer": "  hey, if we know it can we have candy?!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " all right, y\u0092know what? forget it, all of you forget it! you\u0092ve ruined it! go home! you\u0092ve ruined it! you\u0092ve ruined it!", "answer": " that\u0092s right, it\u0092s all ruined! you guys ruined everything! you ruined it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": "  thank you.", "answer": " you\u0092re welcome.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " did you smoke?", "answer": " no! smokes-a-lot lady blew smoke directly into my mouth. eh-uh\u0097are you okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " i\u0092m fine now, but it was really scary there for a while. i mean, someone slipped a-a threatening note under the door.", "answer": "  oh yeah, sorry about that. mob mentality or whatever, i don\u0092t know\u009a  ending credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " i can\u0092t believe it! i did it! i rode a bike! i never thought i\u0092d be able to do that! thank you ross.", "answer": " oh hey, don\u0092t thank me, thank yourself. you\u0092re the one who faced her fears and ultimately overcame them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}]